

S. Mohnish Kumar

Full Stack Developer

My Contact

mohnish101998@gmail.com

(1) 7418667102

Chennai

mohnishwebcraft.xtremerental.shop

Frontend

- HTML
- · CSS
- JavaScript
- Javery
- Bootstrap

Backend

- PHP
- Laravel
- MySQL Database

Education Background

SRM Valliammai Engineering College BE (Mechanical Engineering) - 2020 CGPA - **7.2**

HSC in Oxford MHSS - 2016 Percentage - 88%

SSLC in Oxford MHSS - 2014 Percentage - 96.4%

Certificate

JavaScript Algorithms And Data Structures At FreeCodeCamp

About Me

A professional Full Stack Web Developer with 1.4 years of experience in both front-end and back-end development. I am driven by my passion for web development, which motivates me to create exceptional, user-friendly sites with my coding expertise. I am dedicated to delivering innovative, effective results to the organization .

Professional Experience

eWallHost Web Services | PHP Develper

Jan 2023 - Present

- Develop new product features and build new web pages.
- Optimize On-page SEO content for better SERP visibility and closely monitor its performance.
- Integrate APIs, and employ AJAX for server communication.
- Integrate products/services into the CMS dashboard and oversee content updates with ease and efficiency.

Lead Integrated Business Services | Web Developer Sep 2022-Nov 2022

Specialized in Front-end technologies, including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Additionally, I acquired proficiency in PHP language.

Netaxis IT Solutions | Full Stack Developer

Apr 2022-Jul 2022

Focused on refining my skills in Front-end technologies, including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and did some Front-end tasks.

IM Gears Pvt Ltd | Production Engineer & Quality Inspecter

Feb 2021-Mar 2022

Operating and running CNC machines to manufacture products, as well as ensuring the quality of the manufactured products through rigorous inspection and testing processes.

Live Projects

Static Webstie

- www.rentointegrated.com
- www.elaverointegrated.com
- www.srisaidecors.com

Dynamic Website

- www.mrspecs.xtremerental.shop
- www.shirt-inc.com